Vartan Simoni resume



About me

I am originally Armenian and have lived and worked in several countries. For this reason I speak six different languages . I am electronic engineer by profession and have experience in electronics field. Before my education I worked as a mathematics teacher

Download my CV

Contact

Name : Vartan Simoni

Address: Troensevej 1, 23, Naestved, Denmark

Mobile: +45 91 42 31 34

Mail: albertsimoni2015@gmail.com









Work experience



Technician

Denmark: 2016-2017

Worked as technician for repair of electronic devices.



Technician

Russia: 2002-2013

Worked as technician, installed satellite internet and tv Dishes.



Technician

Russia: 1998-2000

frequency for pagers and tuned and repair them.

Education



Electronics Engineer

1985 - 1993

Master in electronic science, from Armenia



Diplom

1970-1982

High School, Mathematical field, from Iran

Skill's

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

Nodjs

Personality

Problem-Solving Skills 90%

Honesty 95%

Flexibility 95%

Cheerful 95%

Hobby





©VartanSimoni 2020